

CONTACT

P: +33 6 13 87 54 84

Age: 33 ans

E: vincentgueret@hotmail.com

L : www.linkedin.com/in/vincent-gueret-

a1190b56/

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Test Script Test lead Software management and support MS Office (Word, PPT, Visio) Excel (TCD, VBA, PowerQuery) Process operation writing Sharepoint Customer relationship Web development COGNOS and ServiceNow

PERSONAL SKILLS

Adaptability Curiosity Reliable and professional Stress Management Team spirit Fast learner Motivation Reactivity

LANGUAGE

FRENCH: Native ENGLISH : Profesionnal

HOBBIES

Computer and News technologies Sports (soccer, rugby, basketball, bike, running) Music (guitar) Travels History

VINCENT GUERET

SYSTEM LEAD AND RETAIL OPERATION

ABOUT ME

I am an IT enthusiast, with more than seven years of experience in different industries (Automotive, financial, Leasing). I would like to and improve my knowledge and to offer my skills to a company which promotes agility and evolution in an IT environment

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEST LEAD AND RETAIL OPERATION SUPPORT

Opel Bank (Stellantis group)| Jan 2021 - Now

- UAT test coordinator
- Test management and test lead (Regression and Sanity tests)
- · Test script writing
- · Creation of an Invoice system generator (Excel and VBA)
- Process documents creation

OPERATIONAL SOFTWARE LEADER

Opel Bank (Stellantis group)| May 2020 - Dec 2020

- IT support for Sales Account Managers
- Software support and settings management
 Test Management (Team leader in test session)
- IT Service desk Management system creation (EXCEL) Deployment Automation Data and letter management
- Data management and Software management
 Projects development (IT Service Desk Management system with Excel and VBA)

SALES ASSISTANT AND CUSTOMER SERVICES

Rcibanque (Renault Group) | Jul 2015 - Jan 2020

- Contract conformity
- · Dealer relation Customer relationship
- · Litigation management

CUSTOMER SERVICES REPRESENTATIVE

HP (For Opel Brand) | oct 2014 - Jun 2015

- · Customer relationship and litigation management
- CRM onDemand software (ORACLE) key User

CAR SHARING OPERATIONAL SUPPORT

ALPHABET (BMW group) | Mar 2014 - Aug 2014

- · CarSharing fleet management
- Operational system (booking website and car software maintenance)
- · Customer and user relationship Provider service control and SLA management
- Customer relationship and car fleet report
 Process writer and provider relationship
- Reporting

SALES ASSITANT

Arval (Groupe BNP) | sept 2013 - jan 2014

- · Delivery management and sales assistant (UGAP fleet)
- Customer relationship
- · Excel reporting

EDUCATION

BACHELOR Marketing and international businesses

BTS Management Unités Commerciales

IFIDE METZ | 2009 - 2011